Pregnant women are not factories.
Jonathan Hinder MP
Labour · Pendle and Clitheroe
Babies are not goods to be ordered.
Steve Yemm MP
Labour · Mansfield
There are things in our society, Mr Pritchard,
which I believe should never be reduced
to questions around contract and individual choice or intention.
And I’m certain that motherhood is one of those.
Shivani Raja MP
Conservative · Leicester East
A child cannot consent to a surrogacy arrangement.
They cannot understand the promises adults have made.
Jim Shannon MP
DUP · Strangford
Compensation for genuine expenses of carrying a baby is one thing.
Paying a woman for carrying a baby is quite another.
Tracy Gilbert MP
Labour · Edinburgh North and Leith
50% of responses to the Law Commission’s consultation
called for a total ban on surrogacy in the UK.
I fully support that ban.
Dr Neil Shastri-Hurst MP
Conservative · Solihull West and Shirley
We must also speak for the child who cannot speak for his or herself,
and protect the woman who carries and gives birth to that child.